翻译: 笑笑 扭头 alicia 林笑眉
猎鹰一号 我们准备行动吧
Falcon one, do we have a go?
校对: FENGYUDEER
准备好了 猛虎一号
The light is green, tiger one.
你破窗而入的时候打算说什么
What are you gonna say when you crash through the window?
嘿 抱歉突然落进来
Hey, there, sorry for dropping in.
后期: 尘世劫
我都起鸡皮疙瘩了 Jake
Goose bumps, Jake. Goose bumps.
- 装备安全吗  - 安全
- Is the equipment secure?  - Check.
压制: 发烧
- 手枪上膛没  - 上了
- Weapon loaded?  - Check.
你吃早饭了吗
Did you have breakfast?
什么 这不是检查清单里的内容啊
What? That's not on the checklist.
我加上这个是因为我关心你
I added it because I care about you.
- 没 我没吃早饭  - 不能接受
- No, I did not have breakfast. - Unacceptable.
看看你口袋
Look in your pocket.
嘿 这儿有个小巧克力棒
Hey, there's little chocolate chips in this.
没错 我又不是白痴 我知道怎么
Yeah, I'm not an idiot. I know how
骗我最好的朋友补充纤维
to trick my best friend into eating his fiber.
好了 巧克力棒已消化 任务开始
All right, bar digested. Mission go.
- 纽约警察  - 不许动
- NYPD! - Stay where you are!
把手放在我能看见的地方
Hands in the air where I can see 'em!
嗨 抱歉突然落进来
Hey, there, sorry for dropping in.
酷吗 我觉得超酷
Was it cool? It felt really cool.
对对 挺酷的
Yeah. Yeah, it was pretty cool.
挺酷的 哪儿不好了
Pretty cool? What went wrong?
- 没什么  - 你脸上有软糖
- Nothing. - You have fudge on cheek.
哦 早餐棒上的 Boyle
Oh, from the breakfast bar, Boyle!
神烦警探
第三季 第六集
电波诚译
所以我破窗而入 脚先落地
So I smash through the window, feet first.
到处都是碎玻璃 然后我说
There's glass everywhere, and I say,
嘿 抱歉突然落进来了
"Hey, there, sorry for dropping in."
- 吼  - 哇哦
- Ho! - Whoa.
最棒的地方就是 我脸上什么都没有
And the best part is, there was nothing on my cheek.
突然插入这个细节有点奇怪
That's a weird detail to throw in there.
你才是个突然插入的奇怪细节
You're a weird detail to throw in there.
- 嗯 什么  - 等一下 Peralta
- Hmm? What? - Wait a second, Peralta.
你无缘无故打破了一扇窗
You busted through a window for no reason?
警长 这是基本警察战术 要控制每个出口
Basic police tactic, Sarge. Cover every exit.
那是个五楼的密封窗户
It was a sealed window on the fifth floor.
你本可以跟Charles走门进去
You could have just gone in the door with Charles.
对 但那我的口号要是什么
Yeah, but then what would my catchphrase have been?
"当 当 谁啊 正义吗"
"Knock, knock, who's there? Justice"?
哦 那个确实很棒
Ooh, that's actually amazi.
- Charles 写下来  - 已经写了
- Charles, write that down. - Already did.
警长 有什么大不了的
Sarge, what's the big deal?
我们阻止了两千克海洛因流入市面
We stopped two kilos of heroin from hitting the streets.
谁会在乎一扇打破的窗
Who cares about one broken window?
我在乎
I do!
我是那个因为你的愚蠢表演而要花整个周末
I'm the one who has to spend all weekend doing paperwork
写文书的人
because of your dumb stunt.
但 Terry喜欢文书工作
But... Terry loves paperwork?
- 不 Jake 我不喜欢  - 哦
- No, Jake, I do not. - Oh.
我有两个孩子 一份工作和正怀孕的妻子
Look, man, I've got two kids, a job, and a very pregnant wife.
我只有每周日的一个小时属于自己
I get one hour a week to myself on Sundays.
你知道我那个时候干嘛吗
You know what I do with that time?
我泡个热水泡泡浴 把电视推进来
I run a hot bubble bath, wheel in a TV,
然后看体育花絮
and watch sports bloopers.
体育花絮
Sports bloopers?
那很搞笑而且让人放松
They're hilarious and relaxing,
让我的英雄们更人性化了
and they humanize my heroes.
好吧 我破窗而入
Okay, well, I went through a window.
那也算个花絮 对吧
That's a blooper of sorts, right?
不
No!
你有意做的就不是花絮
It's not a blooper if you meant to do it!
谢谢你毁了我的周末
Thanks for ruining my weekend.
这就是个灾难
This is a debacle.
哦 老兄 警长生气了
Oh, man. Sarge is pissed.
我们该怎么办 Jake
What are we gonna do, Jake?
别担心 会好的
Don't worry. It's gonna be fine.
我们只要把这个灾难变成
We just have to turn this debacle
一个绝对的"好运"
into a straight-up "Bacle."
下午
我想我该回去了
Guess I should be getting back.
Ray叔叔 谢谢你借我
Uncle Ray, thank you for loaning me
你最好的警探一起吃饭
you best detective for lunch.
我的荣幸
My pleasure.
当然 根据她的劳工合同
Of course, she is entitled to 45 minutes
她只有45分钟
as per her union contract.
好的 很高兴见到你
Okay, well, great to see you.
拜 宝贝
Bye, baby.
等一下 Diaz警探
A minute, Detective Diaz.
你跟Marcus怎么样了
What's going on with you and Marcus?
你指什么
What are you talking about?
他说"宝贝"时 你肩膀收紧了一下
Your shoulders tightened when he said "Baby."
我问你俩怎么样了的时候
Your nostrils flared when I asked
你的鼻孔微张
what was going on with the two of you.
而且你袖子上有烩菠菜芝士
And you have saag paneer on your sleeve,
鉴于你对印度菜的厌恶
which, given your aversion to Indian cuisine,
这表示你让他选了餐厅
suggests you let him choose the restaurant.
你为什么要这样做
Why would you do that?
- 好意  - 同情
- Kindness. - Pity.
你要跟他分手了
You're about to break up with him.
- 该死 你太棒了  - 嗯嗯
- Damn, you are good. - Mm-hmm.
事情进展的不顺利
Things aren't working out.
我不想多说
I don't want to talk about it.
对于我们已经说过的话我感到后悔
I regret the words we've already spoken.
听着 我可能不应该掺合进来
Listen, I know I probably shouldn't get involved,
但Marcus是我侄子
but Marcus is my nephew,
我希望你能温柔地甩了他
and I hope you'll let him down gently.
别担心
Don't worry.
我不想事情变得尴尬
I don't want things to be awkward.
我打算在他睡觉的时候给他发条短信
I'm gonna send him a text while he's sleeping
"我们结束了"
that says, "We're done."
清楚 准确
Clear. Accurate.
但你觉得那就够了吗
But do you feel like it's enough?
"我们结束了
"We're done.
再见"
Good-bye."
没错 那才对
Yes. That should do it.
怎么了 Peralta
What's going on, Peralta?
Charles说你要让我比
Charles says you're going to make me
我新婚之夜还开心
happier than I was on my wedding night.
呃 要我我可不会这样说的
Well, that's not how I would have put it,
但我知道你生气我毁了你的花絮时间
but I know you were mad at me for ruining blooper time,
所以我做了你所有的文书工作
so I did all your paperwork.
那没用的
That's not helpful.
你总是有几千个错误
You always make a thousand mistakes.
嗯哼 Amy替我做之前
Mm-hmm, that's what Amy said as well
也是这么说的
right before she took over for me,
所以这是完美的
so it's perfect.
好吧 嘿 谢了 老兄
Okay. Hey, thanks, man.
我很感激
I appreciate it.
而且我跟Sharon说了
And I spoke with Sharon.
也跟Holt警长说了
I spoke with Captain Holt.
然后我们都觉得你应该放个假
And we all agree that you deserve a break.
所以这个周末 Charles和我
So this weekend, Charles and I
要带你去个很棒的户外地点
are taking you to the great outdoors
去 Lohank警探的小屋
to Detective Lohank's cabin.
去他的新婚夜
Boom. Suck it, wedding night.
Lohank 那个屌丝
Lohank? That sad sack?
他就知道说他老婆
All he does is talk about his wife
跟别的男人上床
sleeping with other men.
不 他也有些很棒的关于他前列腺癌
No, he also has some great stories
的故事啊
about his prostate cancer.
而且 他不会在旁边待着
Besides, he's not sticking around.
就咱们三个
It's just the three of us.
这话是骗人的
Those woods are full of ticks.
那里就是莱姆病发病中心
It's Lyme disease central.
由扁虱叮咬而出现麻疹、发烧等症状的一种传染性疾病
那就买点杀虫剂
So we'll get some bug spray.
而且那个小屋说不定满是黑霉
Plus that cabin's probably covered in black mold.
- 歧视  - 你知道吗
- Racist. - You know what?
我要待在家里泡个"花絮澡"
I am gonna stay home and have a blooper bath.
哦 别这样 警长
Oh, come on, Sarge.
这会很有趣的
It's gonna be fun.
你还记得 乐趣 吗
You remember fun, right?
这是什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
没什么 就是
Nothing. It's just--
我给咱们计划了一个很棒的男生周末
I planned this awesome guys' weekend for us,
但你想的全是莱姆病
and all you can think about is Lyme disease.
不是真的
Untrue.
我想的是所有的蜱虫疾病
I'm thinking about all tick-borne diseases--
鞭虫病 兔热病 落基山斑疹热
anaplasmosis, tularemia, Rocky Mountain spotted fever.
我可能真需要放松一下
You know, maybe I could just chill out a little.
没错 你压力太大了
Yes. You're stressed.
找点乐子对你有好处 我保证
A little fun would do you good, I promise.
你知道吗 你是对的
You know what? You're right.
你们最好准备好见识 有趣的Terry
You all better get ready for fun Terry.
哦 有趣的是Terry 听起来很有趣
Ooh, fun Terry. He sounds fun.
哦 他很疯狂的
Oh, he's crazy.
谢谢你计划这些 Jake
Thanks for planning this, Jake.
不 谢谢你这么棒
No, thank you for being amazing
而且谢谢你开车带我们去小屋
and also for driving us up to the cabin.
我的车在店里 坐Charles的车
My car's in the shop, and riding in Charles's
就像坐在狗屁股里一样颠
is like sitting inside of a dog's behonkus.
有趣的Terry 等不及见识了
Fun Terry. Can't wait.
嘿 Gina 你能帮我个忙吗
Hey, Gina. Would you do me a favor?
当然 谢谢你问我
Yes, thank you for asking.
我现在不想做这些工作
I did not feel like doing this work right now.
哦 那些看起来像重要文件
Oh, those look like important papers.
怎么了 我怎么帮你
What's up? How can I help?
呃 我还是个小孩的时候
Well, when I was a kid,
我发明了一个磁手电别针
I invented a magnetic flashlight clip
所以我就可以在被子里读书了
so I could read under the covers.
这个别针跟我一起周游了世界
This clip and I went all around the world together--
夏尔郡 甜蜜谷 特雷比西亚
the Shire, Sweet Valley High, Terabithia.
但却没去过朋友家 是吧
But never to a friend's house, huh?
没这个必要
Uncalled for.
反正我意识到这个可能对警察工作
Anyway, I realized that this could be really helpful
真的很有用 所以我跟纽约警察采购
for police work, so I made an appointment
的头儿约了个时间
with the head of NYPD purchasing.
我要把这个卖给他 但我担心
I have to sell him on it, but I'm afraid
我可能让人觉得有些无聊
I might come across a little boring.
Amy 你是在问我
Amy, are you asking me
能不能帮你麻雀变凤凰
to "She's All That" You?
She's All That 美国电影
我没读过那个
I didn't read that.
但如果那是关于帮助朋友的 那没错
But if it's about helping out a friend, then yes.
请帮我麻雀变凤凰吧
Please "She's All That" Me.
好的
Okay.
但如果我们要做这件事
But if we're gonna do this,
我们就要用我的方式做 好吗
we're gonna do it my way, all right?
首先我要把你彻底打碎
First I'm going to need to break you down to nothing
然后再把你一片片拼起来
and then build you back up piece by piece.
见面就在明天
Well, the meeting's tomorrow.
好吧 我们就只把你彻底打碎
Well, we'll just break you down to nothing
然后看看那是什么时候
and see what time it is.
第二天早晨
什么味道
What is that smell?
这是不含尿味的空气
That is the absence of urine.
只有离开了布鲁克林才闻得到
You got to leave Brooklyn to get that.
不含尿味 这个我可以习惯
No urine, I could get used to this.
很好
Oh, yes.
这只是个开始 朋友
And that's just the beginning, my friend.
等你坐到火边
Just wait till you're sitting fireside,
啜着优质中国威士忌
sipping on a premium Chinese Scotch,
抽着上好卢旺达雪茄
and smoking a sweet Rwandan cigar.
蛮好 蛮好
Okay. Okay.
不带那些出产国的话我应该会挺享受的
I probably could have done without the countries of origin,
不过听起来很好了
but that sounds great.
- 是啊  - 你还准备了什么
- Yeah. - What else do you have planned?
可多了 比方说钓鱼
Oh, so much. I'm talking fishing.
比方说扑克 比方说扔飞盘
I'm talking poker, I'm talking Frisbee.
Boyle 还有什么
Boyle, what else am I talking?
采野花来做我们自己的专属古龙水
Wildflower picking so we can make our own cologne.
不 我是想说还有篝火和烤棉花糖巧克力夹心饼干
Nope, I was talking bonfires and s'mores,
但让你接话就是我的错
but that's my fault for throwing to you.
一定会超级有趣的
This is going to be fun as hell.
这将会是史上最有趣的周末
This is going to be the best weekend ever!
欢迎来到臭水坑庄园
Welcome to Stink Puddle Manor.
臭水坑
Stink Puddle?
庄园
Manor.
只是好奇 为什么你
Just out of curiosity, why would you
给自己的房子起名为臭水坑
name your house Stink Puddle?
不是我
Oh, I didn't.
是房屋检查员想出来的
The home inspector came up with it.
做了放射治疗之后我什么都闻不到了
I can't smell anything since the radiation therapy.
又一个有趣的故事 对吧
Another great story, eh?
这里没电 没暖气
So there's no power, no heat.
有自来水吗
Is there running water?
当然有自来水
Of course there's running water.
但我是不会用的
Oh, but I wouldn't use it.
严重污染了
It's very contaminated.
我们有三条狗死在井里了
We had three dogs die in the well.
三条
Three?
如果它们不是被拴在一起
If they weren't all tied together,
我们可能只会失去一条
we might have just lost the one.
惨的是 他们都是我儿子的治疗犬
Sad thing is, they were therapy dogs for my son.
噢
Oh.
我妻子离开后他就有了被遗弃的创伤
He had real abandonment issues after my wife left.
就像是一道情感伤疤上
It was kind of like an emotional scar
又覆上了一道情感伤疤
on an emotional scar.
但树林很赞 对吧
But the woods are super nice, right?
哦是的 是的 可漂亮了
Oh, yeah, yeah. Gorgeous.
除了天坑的季节
Except during sinkhole season.
什么时候是天坑季节
When's sinkhole season?
已经开始了大概 二十年了
It's been going on for, like, 20 years now.
就像<权力的游戏>里的冬天一样
It's kind of like a "Game of Thrones" Winter.
好吧
Right. Yeah.
总之 我把这儿留给你们了
Anyway, I'll leave you guys to it.
玩得开心
Have fun.
别做任何我不会做的事
Don't do anything I wouldn't do.
比方说
For instance,
喝这的水或者让你的妻子
drink the water or let your wife
去出差
go on work trips.
记住了
Duly noted.
你想见我
You wanted to see me?
我跟Kevin说了我赞成
I told Kevin about how I approved
你和Marcus的分手方法这件事
of your strategy for breaking up with Marcus,
然后他说我们是"反社会者"
and he said that we were "Sociopaths."
所以你要离开他了吗
So you're gonna leave him?
不 我觉得他说的或许有理
No, I think he may have a point.
你可能不该只是发一条短信
You might need to do more than simply text.
冗长的分手只会以
A long, drawn-out breakup is just gonna end
一个Marcus痛哭的大场面结束
in a big scene and Marcus crying.
他的感情太丰富了
He has so many emotions.
他们这么深爱对方真是太感天动地了
It's just so beautiful how much they love each other.
这只是个广告
It's a commercial
冰箱广告
for a refrigerator.
是的确实令人却步
Yes, it is daunting.
但我做了些和平分手的调查
But I did some research on amicable breakups.
我查阅了女性健康杂志网
I visited www.Ladiesgoodhealthmag.Com/
第六板块情感在线的第867599904条
6-relationships/867599904/ 9432&20.Html.
- 你知道这网站吗  - 不知道
- Do you know that site? - No.
很显然 如果你理解被甩的人的感觉
Well, apparently, it's less painful
对方痛苦就会少些
if you acknowledge the dumpee's feelings.
- 恶心  - 但别担心
- Ew. - But don't worry.
我们来练习一下
We'll practice. Hmm?
我来当Marcus 开始
I'll be Marcus. Go.
Marcus 我觉得我们应该分手
Marcus, I think we should break up.
这使我难过
That makes me feel sad.
我很难过
I am sad.
我感觉到你的悲伤了
Your sadness is noted.
我感觉被理解了
I feel acknowledged.
谢谢你和我分手
Thank you for breaking up with me.
我需要八分钟把自己的东西收好
It will take me eight minutes to collect my things.
我觉得进行的不错
I think that went very well.
嗯
Hmm.
好了 小溪
Okay, creek.
请给我打包三条新鲜鳟鱼 谢谢
I'd like three fresh trout to go, please.
直接飞上去了
It just went straight up.
现在掉下来了 妈呀
Now it's coming down. Oh, boy!
学着点 失败者们
Watch and learn, losers.
呀
Yah!
- 我没看见它去哪了  - 我脖子后面
- I didn't see where it went. - Back of my neck.
在我脖子后面
It's in the back of my neck.
我从你们的教训中学到了
Okay, I've learned from your mistakes.
不要太用力 放得晚些 还有
Not too hard, late release, and...
挺有趣的 钓鱼挺有趣的
That was fun. Fishing was fun.
- 是啊  - 回小屋吗
- Yeah. - Back to the cabin?
- 好啊  - 好啊
- Yeah. - Yeah.
在我们着手你的演讲前
Before we get into your pitch,
你怎么称呼这个产品
what are you calling the product?
免提照明系统 或者免照灯
The Handless Lighting System, or HLS.
听起来像个基因疾病似的
Sounds like a genetic disorder.
叫肩上新星怎么样
How's about Shoulder Nova?
我喜欢 太棒了
I love it. Amazing.
完美
It's perfect.
现在来说说演讲
Now let's talk presentation.
你的开头什么样的
What's your opener?
嗨 我叫Amy Santiago
Hi, I'm Amy Santiago,
我的产品将会带来很大的改变
and my product will make a real difference.
肩上新星
It is the Shoulder Nova.
我唯一的建议就是 再多百分之一千的魅力吧
My only note is, make it 1000% more captivating.
很好的建议
Very good note. Yeah.
好了
Okay.
我懂了
I got it.
嗯
Mm...
叮
Ding.
噢你们好 我是Amy Santiago
Oh, hello. I'm Amy Santiago.
够有魅力了吗
Was that captivating enough?
奇怪的是 可能有点太有魅力了
Weirdly, it might have been a scooch too captivating.
我的想法是
Here's what I'm thinking.
你可以先坐下
Mm-kay? You can take a seat.
好了
Okay.
直到这一刻 世界都只有黑暗
Until this moment, there was only darkness.
但现在有了
But now there is...
光
light.
我是Vanessa Santiago
I am Vanessa Santiago,
我将会给你们带来震撼
and I'm about to blow your minds.
你想让我把名字改成Vanessa
You want me to change my name to Vanessa?
非常想
Desperately.
不得不说 中国人
I got to say, the Chinese
很懂如何制作难喝的威士忌
know how to make a terrible scotch.
显然是
They certainly do.
好难喝 不过能让你醉
Ugh, it's bad. Gets you drunk, though.
我找到全部的虫了
Well, I found all the worms.
它们在外屋吃一只狐狸的身体
They're eating a fox corpse in the outhouse.
说到这个 我饿了
Speaking of which, I'm getting hungry.
- 晚饭吃什么  - 晚饭
- What's for dinner? - Dinner?
当然啊 晚饭
Yes, of course. Dinner.
你没带食物吗
Did you not pack any food?
外面有新鲜狐狸
There's fresh fox.
不是新鲜的
Oh, it is not fresh.
你认真的吗
Are you serious?
我们来的路上停车三次
We stopped three times on the way up here
就为了买烟花 而你都没有想过买点吃的吗
to buy fireworks, and you never thought to get groceries?
那些冷藏箱里装的是什么
What was in those coolers?
烟花啊
The fireworks.
我以为我们能钓一手好鱼嘛
Look, I thought we would be incredible at fishing.
我相信我们有实力还有错咯
Excuse me for believing in us.
没关系的 别担心
It'll be okay, guys. No need to worry.
我刚上了一个野外觅食的课 不是我吹
I just took a foraging class, and not to brag,
他们都叫我蘑菇大师
I was voted Mr. Fungus.
瞧 蘑菇大师来拯救我们了
Aha, Mr. Fungus to the rescue.
你看 警长 所有问题都可以解决的
See, Sarge, everything's going to work out,
你不用老这么紧张
and you don't have to stress all the time.
Boyle 你真的能给我们找到食物当晚餐吗
Boyle, you really think you can find us dinner?
这个嘛 我保证
Um, let's just say
肯定能有一餐 孢子盛宴
it's gonna be a "Spore-gasbord."
五小时后
Charles肯定出事了 对吧
Something bad happened to Charles, didn't it?
出大事了
Big time.
天哪 要是我们听到的
Oh God, what if the last thing
他最后的话是 孢子盛宴 可咋办
we ever heard him say was "Spore-gasbord?"
Charles Charles
Charles! Charles!
我有些担心了 Jake
I'm starting to get worried, Jake.
放心吧
Relax.
Charles最懂怎么在野外生存了
If anybody can handle it out here, it's Charles.
Into the Woods 美国电影
他在剧院里都看了十遍的"魔法黑森林"
He saw "Into the Woods" Ten times in the theater.
小心点 那是毒藤
Watch it. That's poison ivy.
哇 提醒得好
Whoa. Good call.
我对毒藤过敏
I'm allergic to poison ivy.
以前参加体育训练营的时候
I got it one time at sports camp,
在林子里跟Liz Almont亲热的时候被蛰到过一次
making out in the woods with Liz Almont.
好吧 我们没在亲热
Okay, fine. We weren't making out.
是我在找我的呼吸器
I was looking for my inhaler.
也不是体育训练营 是哮喘夏令营
And it wasn't sports camp. It was asthma camp.
Jake 我们是不是迷路了
Hey, Jake. Are we lost?
啥 没有啊
What? No.
我们在探险
We're on an "Adventure."
对吧 有趣的Terry
Right, Fun Terry?
有趣的Terry已经不存在了
Fun Terry's gone.
他一个小时前饿死了
He starved to death an hour ago.
这个是原版Terry
This is Original Terry.
最可怕的Terry
That's the worst Terry.
你没带地图和手电吗
You didn't bring a map or a flashlight
或者任何能不让我们迷路的东西
or anything that could keep us from getting lost?
这些我都带了
Yes, I brought all of those things.
手机上都有好吗
It's called a cell phone.
地图 手电 指南针
Map. Flashlight. Compass.
还有一个能让我声音变得像T-Pain的软件
An app that makes me sound like T-Pain.
T-Pain 美国歌手
然而现在没电了 所以就只是块砖了
Nope, the battery's dead. Now it's just a brick.
莫慌
But don't freak out.
我也不需要那个变声软件 对吧
I don't need an app to sound like T-Pain, right?
*我们彻底迷路了*
*We're totally lost *
这句听起来更像青蛙卡米特了
Yeah, that was a little more Kermit, but--
你回来啦
Oh, you're back.
分手进行的怎么样
How did the breakup go?
我试着体会他的感受来着
I tried to acknowledge his feelings.
不容易啊 他感受太多了
It wasn't easy. There were a lot of them.
我不明白
I'm just so confused.
很伤心
So sad.
你打算跳窗出去吗
Are you climbing out the window?
没有啊
No.
我又爬了回来 我们又聊了
I climbed back in, and we talked about emotions
20分钟的内心感受
for 20 minutes.
- 天哪  - 没错
- Dear God. - I know.
但我觉得进行的不错
But I think it went well.
起码没人哭
At least there was no crying.
干得不错 Diaz
Well done, Diaz.
你让我这样做其实挺好的
I'm actually really glad you made me do it this way.
我可以告诉他虽然我们分手了
I got to tell him that even though it was ending,
但这段感情对我很重要
it was incredibly meaningful to me,
我会想他的
and I'm gonna miss him.
哦 不
Oh, no.
我就是不希望这个
This is exactly what I didn't want.
你在哭吗
You crying? Oof!
我活该
I deserved that.
Charles死了 而我们就是下一个
Charles is dead, and we're next.
好了 别这么夸张
All right, don't be so melodramatic.
他可能正在啃树皮和浆果呢
He's probably chewing on bark and berries,
玩的很开心 还平平安安的
having the time of his life, safe and sound.
Terry Jake
Terry! Jake!
嘿嘿 我听到了啥
Ho, ho! What's that I hear?
这不是平平安安的Charles Boyle吗
Charles Boyle, safe and sound?
Charles 你说什么
What are you saying, Charles?
你玩得很开心对吗
That you're having the time of your life?
我掉进了一个洞里 还受伤了
I fell in a sinkhole, and I'm badly hurt!
尼玛
Damn it!
Boyle 怎么回事啊
Boyle, what the hell?
我知道 洞很大 对吧
I know. It's a pretty big hole, right?
你怎么会掉下去的啊
How'd you end up down there?
我看到了一颗超漂亮的鸡油菇
I spotted a gorgeous chanterelle.
我伸手去摘 但是扭了一下脚 就掉下来了
I reached for it, but then I rolled my ankle and fell in.
好吧 你别担心 我们这就救你上来
All right, buddy, don't worry. We got you, okay?
我好害怕啊
I was so scared, you guys.
一个占卜的人曾经告诉我我会一个人死在一个坑里
A psychic told me I was gonna die alone in a pit,
我一直告诉自己
and I kept telling myself,
这是个洞 不是坑 是洞 不是坑
"This is a hole, not a pit. This is a hole, not a pit.
这是洞 不是坑
"This is a hole, not a pit.
Charles 这是个洞 不是坑
Charles, it's a hole, not a pit."
好了 拉着我
All right. Here, grab me.
抓住我的手 好吗
Take my hand, all right?
好
Okay.
Terry 把我们拉上去吧
Okay, now pull us up, Terry.
不好了 我在往下滑
Oh crap, I'm slipping!
这不就是Lohank的狗的故事吗
No, it's Lohank's dogs all over again!
肩上新星
免 提 手 电
总而言之
So in conclusion,
除去了手电筒的笨拙
by eliminating flashlight fumbling,
肩上新星
免 提 手 电
肩上新星平均下来可以为警员省下
the Shoulder Nova could save the average police officer
超过13000秒的时间
over 13,000 seconds.
哇 真不少呢 Vanessa
Wow, that sounds like a lot, Vanessa.
没错
It is.
看了只有一件事还没完成了
I guess there's only one thing left to do.
你有权保持
You have the right to remain...
嗷
Uhh!
足够的光线
Well lit!
哇 这个展示太棒了
Wow, that presentation was terrific.
很有趣
So fun to watch.
谢谢 长官
Thank you, sir.
问题在这个产品
See, the problem is the product.
我不觉得有什么用处
I just don't see any need for it at all.
如果我两手都满了的话
I just put the flashlight in my mouth
我一般会把手电筒叼在嘴里
when my hands are full.
可是长官 人体口腔是很脏的
Sir, the human mouth is nasty.
但不要钱啊
Yeah, but mouths are free.
抱歉 我不感兴趣
I'm sorry. I'm just not interested.
好吧 谢谢你花时间看我们的演讲
Okay. Thank you for your time.
你太垃圾了
You are scum.
火生不起来
This isn't working.
- 这次郊游太棒了  - 谢啦
- Great trip, Jake. - Oh, thanks, man.
你明明就知道我是在讽刺你
You know that was sarcastic!
哪里讽刺了
How?
你没带食物 也没带水
You didn't bring food or water
也没问Lohank他的小屋
or ask if Lohank's cabin
是不是从恐怖电影里出来的
was straight out of a horror movie.
现在你又害我们被困在一个坑里
Now you got us trapped in a pit!
这是个洞
Hole.
好吧 我知道现在
Okay, I know that things
情况看起来很糟糕
are not looking great right now,
但你得承认 前面还是玩得很开心的
but you have to admit, you were having fun earlier.
我现在不开心 我从来没这么有压力过
I'm not now. I'm more stressed than ever.
也许是因为你的关注点都在
Maybe that's 'cause you're just focusing
消极的事物上了 Ter熊 你看Charles
on the negative, Ter-bear. I mean, look at Charles.
他很放松啊 我也很放松
He's chill. I'm chill.
那是因为他都被吓傻了 我跟你说
That's 'cause he's in shock! You know what?
你之所以这么放松
The reason you're so chill
是因为你总是让别人收拾你的烂摊子
is because you have everyone cleaning up your messes for you.
没带吃的吗 Charles会去找蘑菇
Didn't bring food? Charles will find mushrooms.
打烂了玻璃吗 Terry会报备的
Smashed through a window? Terry'll do the paperwork.
我报备了啊
Hey, I did the paperwork.
是Amy做的
No, Amy did it!
两位 别吵了好吗
Oh, guys, please, please calm down.
我最讨厌你们吵架了
I hate it when you argue.
让我想起了我爸之前总是和我最好的朋友吵架
It reminds of when my dad used to fight my best friend.
就是我妈
My mom.
我受够了
I'm done with this.
我要睡了
I'm going to sleep.
Charles 跟我抱着睡
Charles, spoon with me.
我们要抱着保暖
We need to huddle together for warmth.
不行 Charles 你是我最好的朋友
No, Charles, you're my best friend.
你要和我抱着睡
You're going to spoon with me.
我先说的
I called first spoon.
Charles 赶快过来
Charles, get over here right now.
Boyle 别为了和Terry的一夜抱
Boyle, don't throw away a lifelong friendship
扔掉了一世的友情
for a one-night spoon with Terry.
好了 我们都别吵了
Okay, enough. We're gonna stop fighting.
我们一起躺下
We're gonna lie down,
像大人一样来个三人抱抱吧
and we're gonna triple-spoon like grown-ups!
快点 来吧 来吧
Come on, bring it in. Bring it in.
看 好了吧
There, okay.
好多了吧 对不
See, that's better, right?
要不要一起唱首歌啊
So do we know any songs?
闭嘴 Charles
Shut up, Charles!
Jake呢 Jake去哪儿了
Jake? Where's Jake?
你是不是把他吃了 Terry
Did you eat him, Terry?
没有
No!
大家早上好啊
Good morning, guys!
你怎么从坑里出去的
How'd you get out of the pit?
简简单单 小事一桩啊
Easy-peasy, lemon squeezy.
其实花了我几个小时
Actually, it took me hours.
我把我所有的衣服绑在一起 再系在一根木头上
I tied all my clothes together, tethered them to a log,
然后当抓钩用
and used it as a grappling hook.
总算钩住一个树根
Managed to snag it in a root.
难道你不冷吗
Aren't you freezing?
一点也不冷
Not at all.
主要是因为这树上的毒藤
Mainly because my skin is in fire
弄的我的皮肤火辣辣的
from all the poison ivy in this tree.
你为什么要那样做
Why'd you do that?
让我猜猜 愚蠢的错误吧
Oh, let me guess. Dumb mistake.
错 是愚蠢的选择
No, dumb choice.
我不想干坐着
I didn't want to sit around and wait for somebody
等着别人来救我
to clean up my mess.
看来我的话你听进去了
Hmm, I guess I got through to you.
是啊
Yeah.
而且你睡着以后 Boyle真的谴责了我
Also, after you fell asleep, Boyle really laid into me.
无情的谴责啊
It was brutal.
我必须得说 Jake 这一次
I got to say, Jake, this time,
我认为你只对了百分之99
I think you're only 99% right.
- 该翻身了  - 不
- We're rolling. - No!
啊
Argh!
你在上面能看到些什么吗
Well, can you see anything from up there?
可以啊 能看到
Yes, I can
臭水坑庄园 太阳方向大概65棵树的距离
Stink Puddle Manor, about 65 trees sunward.
老天 在森林里才呆一天
Man, one day in the woods,
我简直就是无敌探险家了
and I'm freakin' Lewis and Clark up here.
谢谢你过来 Diaz
Thank you for coming, Diaz.
我想为昨天的事道歉
I want to apologize for yesterday.
插手我的下属和我侄子的分手
Inserting myself into my employee's breakup
结果 适得其反
with my nephew somehow, uh, backfired.
不是你的错
It's not your fault.
是我当众出丑 哭得像个傻子
I'm the one that made a scene like a dumb, crying baby.
我考虑去切除我的泪腺
I'm considering having my tear ducts melted shut.
其实有感情并不是件
It's not the end of the world to feel...
坏事
things.
可能吧
I guess not.
确实存在
It's up there.
问题是 我真的很在意Marcus
The thing is, I really care about Marcus,
但是他想结婚
but he wanted to get married,
而我还没准备好
and I'm just not ready for that.
如果像Marcus这么好的人 我都不想嫁
And if I'm not ready with a guy as great as Marcus, then...
那我是不是永远都不想嫁呢
what if I'm never ready?
如果这次
What if that was it,
就是我唯一一次真爱呢
my one chance at love?
如果我再也没有机会了呢
What if I never get a second chance?
我不知道 我只是
I don't know. I'm just...
只是很伤心
I'm just sad.
我懂的
Well, I understand.
一定很难过
It must be very difficult.
等等 你在哭吗
Wait, are you crying?
是啊
Yes.
谢谢你倾听我的感受
Thank you for acknowledging my feelings.
也谢谢你倾听我的
Thank you for acknowledging mine.
咱俩太擅长这个了
We're both great at this.
嘿 朋友
Hey, sport.
你看起来有点"垂丧情低"啊
You look a little D in the D.
垂头丧气 情绪低落 的分别缩写
D for "Down in dumps," Respectively.
如果你还得解释的话
Probably easier to just not abbreviate
那还不如不缩写呢
if you have to explain it.
保留意见
Agree to D.
我想和你谈谈昨天的事
I wanted to talk to you about yesterday.
恩 谢谢你帮我做展示
Yeah, thank you for all your help with the presentation.
抱歉把你的才能浪费在
And I'm sorry you had to waste your talent
这么个愚蠢的产品上
on such a stupid product.
没有你们这种制造者
Without product makers like you,
我们这样的能人哪有机会
us dazzle-doves wouldn't have nothing
发光发热啊
to shake our wings over.
是啊 但是我的发明完全没用
Yeah, but my invention was useless.
才不是 那个人渣说错了
No, that scum was wrong.
我把"肩上新星"给我楼里的一个女孩介绍了
I showed the Shoulder Nova to a girl in my building.
她就像是个小版的你 她非常喜欢
She's like a mini Amy, and she loved it.
她说她要打破快速阅读的
She said she was gonna break the world record
世界纪录
for speed-reading.
切 是啊
Psh! Yeah.
好像一个小女孩能打败Yuri Jurgonav似的
Like some little girl's gonna take down Yuri Jurgonav.
总之 我知道这和你想要的不一样
Anyway, I know it wasn't what you wanted,
但对你还是产生了一点影响的
but you still made a difference.
谢谢你 Gina
Thanks, Gina.
我想我确实"产影"了
I guess I did make a D.
- 别学我的风格  - 好
- Don't steal my thing. - Okay.
- 我就这点要求  - 记住了
- That's all I ask. - I won't.
纽约警局炸弹销毁点
警长
Hey, Sarge.
让我们上来这里干什么啊
Why'd you want us to meet you out here?
谢谢你们陪我过周末
To thank you guys for the weekend.
真的吗 那简直是场灾难啊
Really? It was a total disaster.
也不完全是
Not a total disaster.
没人因为那些死过狗的水而生病啊
None of us got sick from that dog water.
- 你喝了那水  - 没
- You drank that? - No.
听着 Jake 你是对的
Look, Jake, you were right.
我有点忘记怎么找开心了
I have kind of forgotten how to have fun.
我得努力找回来 所以
I'm going to try to work on that, so...
我们回到纽约时
The fireworks you made me surrender
你让我上缴的烟花
when we reentered New York!
嗯哼 有趣Terry回来啦
Uh-huh. Fun Terry's back.
我们来一次把它们全部点燃吧
We're gonna set 'em off in a big pile, all at once.
开枪点燃吗
By shooting our guns at them?
- 什么 不行  - 当然不行
- What? No - No.
我们要像其他人一样正常点燃它们
We're going to set 'em off like normal people.
噢 那也不错
Oh. That's good too.
开始了
Here we go.
看这多好玩啊
See how fun this is?
原来的Terry会担心
Original Terry would have been worried
我们站得太近 需要带安全眼镜
that we're standing too close and need safety goggles,
而他绝对是对的
and he would have been absolutely right.
我们离得太近了 快跑
We're way too close. Run!
电波字幕组 欢迎您的加入
官方网站:www.dbfansub.com
新浪微博:@电波字幕组